var c1_questions = {
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "E1A01",
            "question": "What are the four teams that comprise the overall Project Team?",
            "options": [
                "Owner, Design, Installation, and Management"
            ],
            "answer": "Owner, Design, Installation, and Management"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A02",
            "question": "Who would belong to the Design team?",
            "options": [
                "Anyone with Consultant in their title except the moving consultant"
            ],
            "answer": "Anyone with Consultant in their title except the moving consultant"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A03",
            "question": "Which groups make up the Management Team?",
            "options": [
                "Developer, Construction Manager, and Building Management Agency"
            ],
            "answer": "Developer, Construction Manager, and Building Management Agency"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A04",
            "question": "The End-User, Facility Manager and Building Committee comprise which team within the Project Team?",
            "options": [
                "Owner"
            ],
            "answer": "Owner"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A05",
            "question": "Which group represent the generic roles that are important to the Project process?",
            "options": [
                "Project Managers, Designers and Installers"
            ],
            "answer": "Project Managers, Designers and Installers"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A06",
            "question": "Which project characteristics must be considered in order to determine which method is best suited for a particular project?",
            "options": [
                "Schedule, Size, Type, Complexity, and Procurement Requirements"
            ],
            "answer": "Schedule, Size, Type, Complexity, and Procurement Requirements"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A07",
            "question": "What is an important aspect of funding that has a direct impact on the project process and design/installation?",
            "options": [
                "Technical Support Funding"
            ],
            "answer": "Technical Support Funding"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A08",
            "question": "Whether a construction project is large or small, which milestones must be achieved in a typical schedule?",
            "options": [
                "Programming, Building Design, AV Bid, and Move-In"
            ],
            "answer": "Programming, Building Design, AV Bid, and Move-In"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A09",
            "question": "What type of project is a typical Consultant-Led Design-Bid-Build contract structure good for?",
            "options": [
                "Long term projects with extended project cycles"
            ],
            "answer": "Long term projects with extended project cycles"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A10",
            "question": "What is the risk in using an OFE/Integrator Installed contract structure?",
            "options": [
                "System and infrastructure design and facility functionality may suffer"
            ],
            "answer": "System and infrastructure design and facility functionality may suffer"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A11",
            "question": "What are some of the important project scope and size considerations in selecting an AV provider?",
            "options": [
                "Financial Stability, Current Workload, and Company Credentials"
            ],
            "answer": "Financial Stability, Current Workload, and Company Credentials"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A12",
            "question": "What type of document typically includes Project Size Requirements, Corporate Profile, Team Personnel, and Warranty Response Time?",
            "options": [
                "RFQ"
            ],
            "answer": "RFQ"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A13",
            "question": "What is a significant difference between the Two-Envelope Bid Method and the Qualifications- Based Selection Method?",
            "options": [
                "Negotiate with the highest ranking firm to finalize the contract"
            ],
            "answer": "Negotiate with the highest ranking firm to finalize the contract"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A14",
            "question": "What is one of the disadvantages of contracting the AV integrator to the electrical subcontractor?",
            "options": [
                "More layers of responsibility and communication"
            ],
            "answer": "More layers of responsibility and communication"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A15",
            "question": "When conducting a complete project bid process, what milestone follows the issuing of the RFP?",
            "options": [
                "Pre-Bid Meeting"
            ],
            "answer": "Pre-Bid Meeting"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A16",
            "question": "Under what circumstances would you likely use an A305-1986 form?",
            "options": [
                "Scoring responses to an RFQ"
            ],
            "answer": "Scoring responses to an RFQ"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A17",
            "question": "What is the ideal way to contract an AV integrator?",
            "options": [
                "Directly to the Owner"
            ],
            "answer": "Directly to the Owner"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A18",
            "question": "The process of identifying the activities that end-users need to perform, and developing the functional descriptions of your systems is referred to as:?",
            "options": [
                "Needs Analysis"
            ],
            "answer": "Needs Analysis"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A19",
            "question": "What is the main task of the third Step of the Program Phase of a Project?",
            "options": [
                "Conducting program meetings"
            ],
            "answer": "Conducting program meetings"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A20",
            "question": "What should be included in the written Program Report?",
            "options": [
                "...A conceptual and functional system description"
            ],
            "answer": "...A conceptual and functional system description"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A21",
            "question": "The more accurate means to estimate dimensions of a commercial space during a site inspection would be to?",
            "options": [
                "Count Ceiling Tiles in a drop tile instalation"
            ],
            "answer": "Count Ceiling Tiles in a drop tile instalation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A22",
            "question": "A client requires a new boardroom. The sales person and engineer are sent to the premises to measure the facility and talk to the client. At this stage they should be performing a _",
            "options": [
                "Needs Analysis"
            ],
            "answer": "Needs Analysis"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A23",
            "question": "Sightlines for audience viewing in a given presentation space can be improved by:",
            "options": [
                "Providing a sloped, or stepped, seating arrangement"
            ],
            "answer": "Providing a sloped, or stepped, seating arrangement"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A24",
            "question": "After presenting a proposal, what is the correct plan of action for following up with the client?",
            "options": [
                "Regularly, until a decision is made"
            ],
            "answer": "Regularly, until a decision is made"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A25",
            "question": "AV professionals determine the end user's needs by examining three things: the required applications, the tasks, and the:",
            "options": [
                "Functions to support the applications"
            ],
            "answer": "Functions to support the applications"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A26",
            "question": "When working with a client to design an AV solution for a new conference center, the client requests a detailed budget for the equipment and installation. What phase is the project in?",
            "options": [
                "Design phase"
            ],
            "answer": "Design phase"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A27",
            "question": "The HDTV aspect ratio is equal to which of the following?",
            "options": [
                "1.78:1"
            ],
            "answer": "1.78:1"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A28",
            "question": "Please select the appropriate resolution for SXGA.",
            "options": [
                "1280 x 1024"
            ],
            "answer": "1280 x 1024"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A29",
            "question": "The Brightness control adjusts which level?",
            "options": [
                "Black Level"
            ],
            "answer": "Black Level"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A30",
            "question": "For what purpose would the AV technician designate a loopback internet protocol address in the 127.0.0.1 to 127.255.255.254 range in a network configuration?",
            "options": [
                "To test the local device to see if TCP/IP is working on your system"
            ],
            "answer": "To test the local device to see if TCP/IP is working on your system"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A31",
            "question": "It is important to consider Polar Patterns when____",
            "options": [
                "Selecting Microphones for use at live events"
            ],
            "answer": "Selecting Microphones for use at live events"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A32",
            "question": "When training a new user how to operate the solution that has been provided, which of the following is a best practice?",
            "options": [
                "Provide complete user documentation prior to training"
            ],
            "answer": "Provide complete user documentation prior to training"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A33",
            "question": "What is a benefit of offering a free training session for a client with new equipment?",
            "options": [
                "It is a positive approach for a long-term partnership"
            ],
            "answer": "It is a positive approach for a long-term partnership"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A34",
            "question": "Which phase comes first in a project?",
            "options": [
                "The Program Phase"
            ],
            "answer": "The Program Phase"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A35",
            "question": "A dimmer rack with a constant load capability is powering twenty four incandescent lights during a stage production. The dimmer rack is running on a steady 230VAC supply and averaging approximately 98 amps draw. Suddenly the line voltage drops to 211VAC. Calculate the expected amperage draw.",
            "options": [
                "90 amps"
            ],
            "answer": "90 amps"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A36",
            "question": "When terminating a Category 5e cable with an 8P8C (RJ-45) connector, it is best practice to untwist each wire pair:",
            "options": [
                "As little as possible to get each wire to enter the proper channel in the connector"
            ],
            "answer": "As little as possible to get each wire to enter the proper channel in the connector"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A37",
            "question": "A camera was installed about 180' (55m) from its 1.5A 12v power supply, the power supply is dead, and needs replacing. Assuming that the camera can operate normally within +/- 10% of the power supply voltage, if 18 gauge wire was run initially and an almost 3v drop is present, what is the correct action?",
            "options": [
                "Re-locate the power supply near the camera"
            ],
            "answer": "Re-locate the power supply near the camera"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A38",
            "question": "There is concern about the noise level in an AV rack room. What weight setting on the SPL meter should be used to demonstrate that the noise level doesn't require hearing protection at all times?",
            "options": [
                "A Weighted"
            ],
            "answer": "A Weighted"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A39",
            "question": "On a new construction project, there is a need to verify that power has been installed in the correct place. Who should be contacted to verify this information?",
            "options": [
                "Project Manager"
            ],
            "answer": "Project Manager"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A40",
            "question": "An audio signal is an _____ representation of a sound",
            "options": [
                "Electrical"
            ],
            "answer": "Electrical"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A41",
            "question": "Any sound reinforcement system consists of two equal parts: the electronic system used to manipulate the audio signal and",
            "options": [
                "The acoustical environment"
            ],
            "answer": "The acoustical environment"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A42",
            "question": "What type of loudspeaker system is typically made up of speakers strategically suspended overhead or placed in the ceiling and may use center-to-center overlap?",
            "options": [
                "Cluster"
            ],
            "answer": "Cluster"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A43",
            "question": "The study of sound-wave motion and sound behavior is the science of",
            "options": [
                "The Study of Acoustics"
            ],
            "answer": "The Study of Acoustics"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A44",
            "question": "Which type of sound is most intelligible?",
            "options": [
                "Direct sound"
            ],
            "answer": "Direct sound"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A45",
            "question": "Sound that bounces off of many surfaces before reaching the listener is called ______ sound",
            "options": [
                "Reverberant"
            ],
            "answer": "Reverberant"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A46",
            "question": "Sound waves have a time relationship to each other known as",
            "options": [
                "Phase"
            ],
            "answer": "Phase"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A47",
            "question": "When sound waves are 180 degrees out of phase what happens?",
            "options": [
                "Phase cancellation"
            ],
            "answer": "Phase cancellation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A48",
            "question": "Decibels are always expressed as a(n) ______ of two quantities.",
            "options": [
                "Ratio"
            ],
            "answer": "Ratio"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A49",
            "question": "A dB may be used to express or describe",
            "options": [
                "SPL"
            ],
            "answer": "SPL"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A50",
            "question": "All sounds start with physical motion, such as vibrating string. This causes adjacent air molecules to push together, or _______",
            "options": [
                "Rarefy. A wavelength is measured at the starting points of two consecutive Cycles"
            ],
            "answer": "Rarefy. A wavelength is measured at the starting points of two consecutive Cycles"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A51",
            "question": "A wavelength is measured at the starting points of two consecutive",
            "options": [
                "Cycles"
            ],
            "answer": "Cycles"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A52",
            "question": "Sound level decreases _______dB every time the source to listener distance is doubled.",
            "options": [
                "6"
            ],
            "answer": "6"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A53",
            "question": "Hertz is the unit of measure for",
            "options": [
                "Frequency"
            ],
            "answer": "Frequency"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A54",
            "question": "One Hertz is equivalent to",
            "options": [
                "One cycle per second"
            ],
            "answer": "One cycle per second"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A55",
            "question": "The distance between the optical center of a lens and the image plane is called the",
            "options": [
                "Focal length"
            ],
            "answer": "Focal length"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A56",
            "question": "The amount of light passed through the lens to the imager on a video camera is controlled by the",
            "options": [
                "Iris"
            ],
            "answer": "Iris"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A57",
            "question": "An R-Y, B-Y, Y video signal is also known as a(n) ______video signal",
            "options": [
                "Component"
            ],
            "answer": "Component"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A58",
            "question": "During video production, removing all of one color from the main image and replacing it with a second image is called a(n) ______",
            "options": [
                "Chroma key"
            ],
            "answer": "Chroma key"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A59",
            "question": "Which of the following incorporates color difference signals?",
            "options": [
                "Y, R-Y, B-Y"
            ],
            "answer": "Y, R-Y, B-Y"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A60",
            "question": "In a video system, using a single electronic reference for timing of all the connected equipment is called ________",
            "options": [
                "Genlock"
            ],
            "answer": "Genlock"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A61",
            "question": "Which device corrects for jitter in an analog video signal?",
            "options": [
                "Time base Corrector"
            ],
            "answer": "Time base Corrector"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A62",
            "question": "In a composite video signal, what determines the brightness?",
            "options": [
                "Amplitude"
            ],
            "answer": "Amplitude"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A63",
            "question": "Specialized devices that display the color hue information in the video signal are called",
            "options": [
                "Vectorscopes"
            ],
            "answer": "Vectorscopes"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A64",
            "question": "Which display technology uses light passing through a medium to create an image?",
            "options": [
                "Transmissive"
            ],
            "answer": "Transmissive"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A65",
            "question": "The aspect ratio for a 1024 x 768 computer display is",
            "options": [
                "4:3"
            ],
            "answer": "4:3"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A66",
            "question": "The ratio of image width to image height is defined as the",
            "options": [
                "Aspect ratio"
            ],
            "answer": "Aspect ratio"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A67",
            "question": "The broadcast video standard used in North America and parts of South America and Asia is",
            "options": [
                "PAL"
            ],
            "answer": "PAL"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A68",
            "question": "Which projector element is covered with tiny mirrors to produce a video or data image?",
            "options": [
                "DMD"
            ],
            "answer": "DMD"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A69",
            "question": "What is the fundamental unit of measure on a fixed resolution display",
            "options": [
                "PIXEL"
            ],
            "answer": "PIXEL"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A70",
            "question": "In a fixed resolution display, the greater the resolution capability the",
            "options": [
                "Greater the number of pixels"
            ],
            "answer": "Greater the number of pixels"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A71",
            "question": "A common technique for reducing the depth requirements of a rear projection space is",
            "options": [
                "Folding the light path"
            ],
            "answer": "Folding the light path"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A72",
            "question": "The changing of direction of a light or sound ray is called",
            "options": [
                "Refraction"
            ],
            "answer": "Refraction"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A73",
            "question": "Light passing through the edges of a lens at different focal lengths results in a blurred image. This is called__",
            "options": [
                "Spherical aberration"
            ],
            "answer": "Spherical aberration"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A74",
            "question": "Which type of front screen has a smooth non-gloss surface similar to a white sheet, provides good color rendition, and evenly disperses light?",
            "options": [
                "Matte"
            ],
            "answer": "Matte"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A75",
            "question": "The higher the color temperature of a light source, the _____ white ligh",
            "options": [
                "Bluer"
            ],
            "answer": "Bluer"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A76",
            "question": "The maximum viewing distance for viewing a displayed image is based on the",
            "options": [
                "Amount of detail in the image"
            ],
            "answer": "Amount of detail in the image"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A77",
            "question": "For good viewing, projected images should not be viewed at angles greater than _____degrees off of the projection axis",
            "options": [
                "45"
            ],
            "answer": "45"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A78",
            "question": "A single video or audio output is converted into multiple outputs to be distributed to the system by using a",
            "options": [
                "DA"
            ],
            "answer": "DA"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A79",
            "question": "Which connector has a solid center pin with an outside sleeve and creates a pressure-fit type connection with its mate?",
            "options": [
                "RCA"
            ],
            "answer": "RCA"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A80",
            "question": "A cable with one conductor and a shield is",
            "options": [
                "Unbalanced"
            ],
            "answer": "Unbalanced"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A81",
            "question": "A _____ bit display will display 65,536 colors.",
            "options": [
                "16"
            ],
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A82",
            "question": "An 8-bit digital word is called a",
            "options": [
                "BYTE"
            ],
            "answer": "BYTE"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A83",
            "question": "Digital signals are a stream of",
            "options": [
                "1's and 0's"
            ],
            "answer": "1's and 0's"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A84",
            "question": "The process of adding video and/or audio signals to an existing signal on a predetermined carrier frequency is called",
            "options": [
                "Modulation"
            ],
            "answer": "Modulation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A85",
            "question": "As the bandwidth of a display system increases, the potential resolution of the images is",
            "options": [
                "Increased"
            ],
            "answer": "Increased"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A86",
            "question": "In a cable, the dielectric",
            "options": [
                "Insulates and separates two conductors"
            ],
            "answer": "Insulates and separates two conductors"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A87",
            "question": "The flow of electrons through a conductor is called",
            "options": [
                "Current"
            ],
            "answer": "Current"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A88",
            "question": "When comparing the relationship of current to voltage and resistance, current is:",
            "options": [
                "Directly proportional to the voltage and inversely proportional resistance"
            ],
            "answer": "Directly proportional to the voltage and inversely proportional resistance"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A89",
            "question": "Which two parameters play a key role during the initial assessment of an AV project?",
            "options": [
                "Project schedule, Project Size"
            ],
            "answer": "Project schedule, Project Size"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A90",
            "question": "Technical support funding can include money for training and ___.",
            "options": [
                "Hiring additional staff"
            ],
            "answer": "Hiring additional staff"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A91",
            "question": "A successful project is an AV system that meets the original design___, fulfills the needs of the___, and remains in proper working order.",
            "options": [
                "Intention, user"
            ],
            "answer": "Intention, user"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A92",
            "question": "Which type of warranty typically involves additional costs and adjustments to meet the owner's needs?",
            "options": [
                "Service agreement"
            ],
            "answer": "Service agreement"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A93",
            "question": "When training users during the System Commissioning and Training Phase, ___ groups allow for more hands-on time with the system.",
            "options": [
                "Smaller (up to six)"
            ],
            "answer": "Smaller (up to six)"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A94",
            "question": "Verification and optimization are two concepts that are applied during System Commissioning to ensure that:",
            "options": [
                "The design intent has been met"
            ],
            "answer": "The design intent has been met"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A95",
            "question": "One way to efficiently manage a construction schedule is to use a ____.",
            "options": [
                "Gantt chart"
            ],
            "answer": "Gantt chart"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A96",
            "question": "During the Construction Phase, what is likely to happen if a product is suddenly discontinued?",
            "options": [
                "A request for change (RFC) may be submitted"
            ],
            "answer": "A request for change (RFC) may be submitted"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A97",
            "question": "During shop testing, ___ is/are checked and ___ is/are tested.",
            "options": [
                "Proper functioning of equipment, software"
            ],
            "answer": "Proper functioning of equipment, software"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A98",
            "question": "Proper functioning of equipment, software",
            "options": [
                "Site Installation"
            ],
            "answer": "Site Installation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A99",
            "question": "Where does the initial testing of a pre-assembled AV system typically occur in the Construction Phase?",
            "options": [
                "At the warehouse, when the equipment is delivered"
            ],
            "answer": "At the warehouse, when the equipment is delivered"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A100",
            "question": "During the Design Phase, it is important to coordinate with which of the following trades?",
            "options": [
                "Architect, electrical consultant, construction manager"
            ],
            "answer": "Architect, electrical consultant, construction manager"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A101",
            "question": "The more accurate means to estimate dimensions of a commercial space during a site inspection would be to?",
            "options": [
                "Count the number of ceiling tiles in a drop tile instalation"
            ],
            "answer": "Count the number of ceiling tiles in a drop tile instalation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A102",
            "question": "A client requires a new boardroom. The sales person and engineer are sent to the premises to measure the facility and talk to the client. At this stage they should be performing a",
            "options": [
                "Needs Analysis"
            ],
            "answer": "Needs Analysis"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A103",
            "question": "What type of interview questions will help a client become interested in a new or unfamiliar technology?",
            "options": [
                "Leading Questions"
            ],
            "answer": "Leading Questions"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A104",
            "question": "As a courtesy before leaving the final needs analysis meeting, the customer should be advised about:",
            "options": [
                "When to expect the proposal"
            ],
            "answer": "When to expect the proposal"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A105",
            "question": "When establishing initial contact with a client, try to develop a relationship early on with the",
            "options": [
                "Stake Holders"
            ],
            "answer": "Stake Holders"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A106",
            "question": "The process of creating an AV solution begins with",
            "options": [
                "Performing a needs analysis"
            ],
            "answer": "Performing a needs analysis"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A107",
            "question": "Which of the following is defined as highly efficient?",
            "options": [
                "LED Lamp"
            ],
            "answer": "LED Lamp"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A108",
            "question": "To maximize the quality of projected images in a presentation you should ensure:",
            "options": [
                "The ambient light is controlled in the presentation area"
            ],
            "answer": "The ambient light is controlled in the presentation area"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A109",
            "question": "Using best practices, determine maximum viewer distance by multiplying the text height by:",
            "options": [
                "150"
            ],
            "answer": "150"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A110",
            "question": "The correct time to discuss visible finishes for wall plates, surface mount speakers, and wall mounted screen casings is during the:",
            "options": [
                "Site Survey"
            ],
            "answer": "Site Survey"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A111",
            "question": "During a site survey, the room appears to have a lot of reverberation present. What treatment could be recommended to improve the sound in the room?",
            "options": [
                "Use more softer, diffuse surfaces"
            ],
            "answer": "Use more softer, diffuse surfaces"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A112",
            "question": "Direct coupled loudspeakers are usually listed by size, frequency response, power handling capacity, and",
            "options": [
                "Impedance"
            ],
            "answer": "Impedance"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A113",
            "question": "When developing an AV solution for a client, whose input is MOST crucial for determining system requirements?",
            "options": [
                "The End User"
            ],
            "answer": "The End User"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A114",
            "question": "What type of connector is this?",
            "options": [
                "BNC"
            ],
            "answer": "BNC"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A115",
            "question": "Bluetooth technology can be useful in AV systems because it",
            "options": [
                "Allows additional connections for control of devices."
            ],
            "answer": "Allows additional connections for control of devices."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A116",
            "question": "When working with a new technician, what is the best way to maintain quality control?",
            "options": [
                "Provide training, enforce standards, and conduct observations"
            ],
            "answer": "Provide training, enforce standards, and conduct observations"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A117",
            "question": "When conducting a client needs analysis to prepare the program report or brief, how does the AV professional determine the end user's needs in a given project?",
            "options": [
                "Ascertain the specific activities the client wants to accomplish"
            ],
            "answer": "Ascertain the specific activities the client wants to accomplish"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A118",
            "question": "A fundamental step in supporting the end user's needs is",
            "options": [
                "determining the overall function of the room or facility type"
            ],
            "answer": "determining the overall function of the room or facility type"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A119",
            "question": "What constraints on working at a site need to be noted when collecting site information?",
            "options": [
                "Limitations on activities, time of day, parking & loading, noise"
            ],
            "answer": "Limitations on activities, time of day, parking & loading, noise"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A120",
            "question": "What factors impact acoustic quality in a given space or venue?",
            "options": [
                "Dimensions and shape of the venue/room; reflected sound and ambient noise"
            ],
            "answer": "Dimensions and shape of the venue/room; reflected sound and ambient noise"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A121",
            "question": "To maximize the quality of projected images in a presentation you should ensure",
            "options": [
                "That ambient light is controlled in the presentation area"
            ],
            "answer": "That ambient light is controlled in the presentation area"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A122",
            "question": "How can you address ambient noise issues in a room?",
            "options": [
                "Use acoustically absorptive materials in the room."
            ],
            "answer": "Use acoustically absorptive materials in the room."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A123",
            "question": "Sightlines for audience viewing in a given presentation space can be improved by:",
            "options": [
                "providing a sloped, or stepped, seating arrangement"
            ],
            "answer": "providing a sloped, or stepped, seating arrangement"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A124",
            "question": "In the program phase, what must be determined to assure that a functional AV system scope will be created?",
            "options": [
                "The specific functions, tasks, and applications of the presenter."
            ],
            "answer": "The specific functions, tasks, and applications of the presenter."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A125",
            "question": "In the program report phase of a site analysis what type of documentation is needed?",
            "options": [
                "Architectural and engineering drawings, industry standards, owner/end user information"
            ],
            "answer": "Architectural and engineering drawings, industry standards, owner/end user information"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A126",
            "question": "How does the AV team present the program report to obtain client approval?",
            "options": [
                "Create a detailed meeting agenda and be sure to document client feedback & suggestions"
            ],
            "answer": "Create a detailed meeting agenda and be sure to document client feedback & suggestions"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A127",
            "question": "How are lighting requirements determined for a given amount of space in a venue?",
            "options": [
                "As the distance from a light source is doubled, perceived illumination decreases by 75%"
            ],
            "answer": "As the distance from a light source is doubled, perceived illumination decreases by 75%"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A128",
            "question": "What should be included in an AV proposal for a client?",
            "options": [
                "Detailed description of all components, accessories, and all costs"
            ],
            "answer": "Detailed description of all components, accessories, and all costs"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A129",
            "question": "In presenting a proposal for AV, what is necessary for a contract?",
            "options": [
                "Statement of specific work proposed, costs and payment schedule, delivery schedule"
            ],
            "answer": "Statement of specific work proposed, costs and payment schedule, delivery schedule"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A130",
            "question": "How do you maintain a proper focus on customer needs and service?",
            "options": [
                "Listen to customer concerns and try to accommodate immediately if it is feasible."
            ],
            "answer": "Listen to customer concerns and try to accommodate immediately if it is feasible."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A131",
            "question": "After hearing the vendors' Request for Proposal (RFP), how do you evaluate the vendor's proposal to determine the best value?",
            "options": [
                "Consider the price, quality, approach, and ability of vendor to fulfill the contract"
            ],
            "answer": "Consider the price, quality, approach, and ability of vendor to fulfill the contract"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A132",
            "question": "How is a contract awarded to a vendor after the vendor is determined to be the best value for a project?",
            "options": [
                "Use the RFP and vendor proposal, negotiate items needing clarification with contract clauses"
            ],
            "answer": "Use the RFP and vendor proposal, negotiate items needing clarification with contract clauses"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A133",
            "question": "In marketing, what is your AV Company's 'value proposition'?",
            "options": [
                "Product or service offering which makes your company better or different from others."
            ],
            "answer": "Product or service offering which makes your company better or different from others."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A134",
            "question": "How should you establish a marketing budget for your AV Company",
            "options": [
                "Set the marketing and advertising budget as a percentage of projected sales."
            ],
            "answer": "Set the marketing and advertising budget as a percentage of projected sales."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A135",
            "question": "When terminating an Ethernet cable, what connector type is normally used?",
            "options": [
                "RJ45"
            ],
            "answer": "RJ45"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A136",
            "question": "What must be considered during rack assembly?",
            "options": [
                "Ergonomics of equipment placement, signal separation, heat load, weight distribution."
            ],
            "answer": "Ergonomics of equipment placement, signal separation, heat load, weight distribution."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A137",
            "question": "If you are projecting onto a screen that is 10 feet (3 meters) wide and your projection distance to screenwidth ratio is 2.0:1, what should be the distance of the projector from the screen?",
            "options": [
                "20 feet (6 meters)"
            ],
            "answer": "20 feet (6 meters)"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A138",
            "question": "When checking signal flow, the FIRST thing you need to confirm is that the signal is:",
            "options": [
                "being generated by the source components."
            ],
            "answer": "being generated by the source components."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A139",
            "question": "During the commissioning process for an AV system installation, how will the AV technician confirm thatthe video display system is working properly?",
            "options": [
                "Connect display devices to a test signal generator, calibrate at points along the path."
            ],
            "answer": "Connect display devices to a test signal generator, calibrate at points along the path."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A140",
            "question": "At the end of an event how does one quickly and safely strike the event?",
            "options": [
                "Strike equipment by category and divide into teams."
            ],
            "answer": "Strike equipment by category and divide into teams."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A141",
            "question": "What are the two main components of a projector that need to be maintained",
            "options": [
                "Air Filter and Lamps"
            ],
            "answer": "Air Filter and Lamps"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A142",
            "question": "Why is it very important to document all changes or update activities on an AV system whenever they are performed?",
            "options": [
                "To manage and maintain the system successfully over time."
            ],
            "answer": "To manage and maintain the system successfully over time."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A143",
            "question": "How does the AV manager maintain good relationships with suppliers and vendors?",
            "options": [
                "Document all transactions, resolve concerns in a professional manner."
            ],
            "answer": "Document all transactions, resolve concerns in a professional manner."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A144",
            "question": "What should be done when you receive a call that there is no sound in a room for an AV event?",
            "options": [
                "Check microphone, batteries, and power switches to assure they are on."
            ],
            "answer": "Check microphone, batteries, and power switches to assure they are on."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A145",
            "question": "What is a logic network diagram used for in AV management activities?",
            "options": [
                "To define project tasks and how they are related."
            ],
            "answer": "To define project tasks and how they are related."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A146",
            "question": "What type of diagram is this?",
            "options": [
                "Gantt Chart"
            ],
            "answer": "Gantt Chart"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A147",
            "question": "Employee evaluations must include:",
            "options": [
                "Documentation of All standards"
            ],
            "answer": "Documentation of All standards"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A148",
            "question": "When properly addressing problems with staff performance or behavior the supervisor must be sure to:",
            "options": [
                "Clearly identify and document the problem behavior and instances of it."
            ],
            "answer": "Clearly identify and document the problem behavior and instances of it."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A149",
            "question": "When creating estimates for an AV project what are the primary considerations?",
            "options": [
                "Equipment & material costs, labor costs, estimate markup."
            ],
            "answer": "Equipment & material costs, labor costs, estimate markup."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A150",
            "question": "When purchasing AV supplies and equipment for a client AV installation project what needs to be done?",
            "options": [
                "Identify needed equipment, tools and labor, work with vendors for prices and delivery schedule."
            ],
            "answer": "Identify needed equipment, tools and labor, work with vendors for prices and delivery schedule."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A151",
            "question": "How can labor timesheets and invoices from previous jobs be used to increase efficiency for future AVjob estimates?",
            "options": [
                "Analysis of past costs for labor and shipping."
            ],
            "answer": "Analysis of past costs for labor and shipping."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A152",
            "question": "A ________ can be useful by tracking the costs of equipment, materials, and labor for each aspect of a projectto determine if these exceeded budgeted amounts.",
            "options": [
                "A job cost analysis"
            ],
            "answer": "A job cost analysis"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A153",
            "question": "A laptop input on a lectern is not working. The interface is connected to a 5 BNC wall plate. The interface is receiving signal and the projector is on the correct input. What is the next step in troubleshooting theissue?",
            "options": [
                "Reverse the H and V sync cables."
            ],
            "answer": "Reverse the H and V sync cables."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A154",
            "question": "What should be done if a touch screen control panel is reportedly locked up, frozen, or other wise reported to be not functioning?",
            "options": [
                "Check all connectors, confirm the screen is not in power saver mode."
            ],
            "answer": "Check all connectors, confirm the screen is not in power saver mode."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A155",
            "question": "What should you do if the audio system is emitting a high frequency hiss, or a waterfall sound?",
            "options": [
                "Check inputs on the mixer, make sure not set too low, check all input gains"
            ],
            "answer": "Check inputs on the mixer, make sure not set too low, check all input gains"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A156",
            "question": "Direct coupled loudspeakers are usually listed by size, frequency response, power handling capacity, and",
            "options": [
                "Impedance"
            ],
            "answer": "Impedance"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A157",
            "question": "When developing an AV solution for a client, whose input is MOST crucial for determining system requirements?",
            "options": [
                "The end users"
            ],
            "answer": "The end users"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A158",
            "question": "Which of the following is NOT a crucial step when developing a marketing message?",
            "options": [
                "Determine the sales commission"
            ],
            "answer": "Determine the sales commission"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A159",
            "question": "What is the formula for calculating current using Ohm's Law?",
            "options": [
                "I = V/R"
            ],
            "answer": "I = V/R"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A160",
            "question": "What is one of the major considerations in creating an AV solution for an important historical site?",
            "options": [
                "Preservation of the site"
            ],
            "answer": "Preservation of the site"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A161",
            "question": "Good customer service is crucial for",
            "options": [
                "Building good customer relationships"
            ],
            "answer": "Building good customer relationships"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A162",
            "question": "What type of connector is shown?",
            "options": [
                "XLR"
            ],
            "answer": "XLR"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A163",
            "question": "When negotiating a contract for a job that will take a long time to complete, one should consider",
            "options": [
                "Progress, stage, or interim invoicing"
            ],
            "answer": "Progress, stage, or interim invoicing"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A164",
            "question": "When conducting a site visit, if a ladder is needed what type should be used?",
            "options": [
                "Fiberglass or wood."
            ],
            "answer": "Fiberglass or wood."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A165",
            "question": "If the displayed text size in a projection presentation is 2-inch/50-mm then the viewer should not befarther away than:",
            "options": [
                "300 inches/7,620 mm"
            ],
            "answer": "300 inches/7,620 mm"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A166",
            "question": "What are the 4 parts of the needs analysis pyramid",
            "options": [
                "Needs, Applications, Tasks, Features and Functions"
            ],
            "answer": "Needs, Applications, Tasks, Features and Functions"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A167",
            "question": "What is a need",
            "options": [
                "An essential function that must be part of an AV system"
            ],
            "answer": "An essential function that must be part of an AV system"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A168",
            "question": "What is an Application",
            "options": [
                "An Activity or function that supports the end users need (Meeting or demo)"
            ],
            "answer": "An Activity or function that supports the end users need (Meeting or demo)"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A169",
            "question": "What is a task",
            "options": [
                "An AV System or process that supports the end users application (A display for a meeting)"
            ],
            "answer": "An AV System or process that supports the end users application (A display for a meeting)"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A170",
            "question": "What is a Function",
            "options": [
                "the specific parts of a task (type ofdisplay, seating layout)"
            ],
            "answer": "the specific parts of a task (type ofdisplay, seating layout)"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A171",
            "question": "A room is going to be used to inform new hires about organizational procedures. What is the Application",
            "options": [
                "Informing new hires"
            ],
            "answer": "Informing new hires"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A172",
            "question": "what is benchmarking?",
            "options": [
                "examining methods, techniques, and principles from peer organizations and facilities, which can be used as a basis for designing a new or renovated facility."
            ],
            "answer": "examining methods, techniques, and principles from peer organizations and facilities, which can be used as a basis for designing a new or renovated facility."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A173",
            "question": "What is the goal of Benchmarking",
            "options": [
                "to identify the AV features and functions desired by the client."
            ],
            "answer": "to identify the AV features and functions desired by the client."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A174",
            "question": "What is a program meeting?",
            "options": [
                "program meeting gathers and exchanges the information necessary to determine which functions are required to support the end users' applications."
            ],
            "answer": "program meeting gathers and exchanges the information necessary to determine which functions are required to support the end users' applications."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A175",
            "question": "What is the program report?",
            "options": [
                "program report is a document that describes the client's specific needs, system purpose and functionality, and the designer's best estimate of probable cost, in a non-technical format for review and approval by the owner."
            ],
            "answer": "program report is a document that describes the client's specific needs, system purpose and functionality, and the designer's best estimate of probable cost, in a non-technical format for review and approval by the owner."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A176",
            "question": "What is the goal of an effective program meeting?",
            "options": [
                "Gather and exchange the information necessary to determine which functions are required to support the end users' applications"
            ],
            "answer": "Gather and exchange the information necessary to determine which functions are required to support the end users' applications"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A177",
            "question": "The main purpose of the program report is to list the equipment and model numbers that will be used in the final system",
            "options": [
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A178",
            "question": "A fundamental step in supporting the end user's needs is:",
            "options": [
                "determining the overall function of the room or facility type"
            ],
            "answer": "determining the overall function of the room or facility type"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A179",
            "question": "In the program phase, what must be determined to assure that a functional AV system scope will be created?",
            "options": [
                "The specific functions, tasks, and applications of the presenter"
            ],
            "answer": "The specific functions, tasks, and applications of the presenter"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A180",
            "question": "How does the AV team present the program report to obtain client approval?",
            "options": [
                "Create a detailed meeting agenda and be sure to document client feedback and suggestions"
            ],
            "answer": "Create a detailed meeting agenda and be sure to document client feedback and suggestions"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A181",
            "question": "What is the conversion of inches to millimeter",
            "options": [
                "1 inch = 25.4 mm"
            ],
            "answer": "1 inch = 25.4 mm"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A182",
            "question": "What is the conversion from feet to meters",
            "options": [
                "1 ft = .3048"
            ],
            "answer": "1 ft = .3048"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A183",
            "question": "1 mm = how many inches",
            "options": [
                ".0393"
            ],
            "answer": ".0393"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A184",
            "question": "A complete project documentation package includes:",
            "options": [
                "Contract documents, Project specifications, Project drawings: architectural and system"
            ],
            "answer": "Contract documents, Project specifications, Project drawings: architectural and system"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A185",
            "question": "What are contract documents",
            "options": [
                "include bid information, contractor qualification requirements, payment schedules, and points of contact."
            ],
            "answer": "include bid information, contractor qualification requirements, payment schedules, and points of contact."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A186",
            "question": "What are project specifications",
            "options": [
                "They are specifications for the project itself. Such as find details of the system."
            ],
            "answer": "They are specifications for the project itself. Such as find details of the system."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A187",
            "question": "What is a section cut flag arrow",
            "options": [
                "Shows the direction of the section drawing"
            ],
            "answer": "Shows the direction of the section drawing"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A188",
            "question": "What is a Detail Drawing",
            "options": [
                "indicate small items that need magnified views in order to show how they must be installed."
            ],
            "answer": "indicate small items that need magnified views in order to show how they must be installed."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A189",
            "question": "What is a section drawing",
            "options": [
                "shows the space as if it was cut apart"
            ],
            "answer": "shows the space as if it was cut apart"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A190",
            "question": "What is an Elevation drawing",
            "options": [
                "is a drawing that looks at the environment from a front, side, or back view"
            ],
            "answer": "is a drawing that looks at the environment from a front, side, or back view"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A191",
            "question": "What is a column line",
            "options": [
                "used to indicate the locations of columns, load-bearing walls, and other structural elements within the building layout"
            ],
            "answer": "used to indicate the locations of columns, load-bearing walls, and other structural elements within the building layout"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A192",
            "question": "What are match lines",
            "options": [
                "show how each sub-drawing matches to another page of the drawing."
            ],
            "answer": "show how each sub-drawing matches to another page of the drawing."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A193",
            "question": "What is a reference flag?",
            "options": [
                "reference flag symbol on a drawing tells us to reference another drawing"
            ],
            "answer": "reference flag symbol on a drawing tells us to reference another drawing"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A194",
            "question": "What are eleveation flags",
            "options": [
                "plan drawings to indicate related elevation drawings."
            ],
            "answer": "plan drawings to indicate related elevation drawings."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A195",
            "question": "What are section cut flags",
            "options": [
                "indicate which section drawing depicts a section of a master drawing in more detail, as shown in the picture."
            ],
            "answer": "indicate which section drawing depicts a section of a master drawing in more detail, as shown in the picture."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A196",
            "question": "What is :AS",
            "options": [
                "Above Slab"
            ],
            "answer": "Above Slab"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A197",
            "question": "What is CL",
            "options": [
                "Center Line"
            ],
            "answer": "Center Line"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A198",
            "question": "What is CM",
            "options": [
                "Construction manager"
            ],
            "answer": "Construction manager"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A199",
            "question": "What is Dia",
            "options": [
                "Diameter"
            ],
            "answer": "Diameter"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A200",
            "question": "What is E.C.",
            "options": [
                "Empty Conduit"
            ],
            "answer": "Empty Conduit"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A201",
            "question": "What is VIF",
            "options": [
                "Verified in field"
            ],
            "answer": "Verified in field"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A202",
            "question": "The farthest viewer concept addresses which three factors?",
            "options": [
                "Image height, viewer task, and distance"
            ],
            "answer": "Image height, viewer task, and distance"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A203",
            "question": "The primary goal of the farthest viewer formula is to ensure that",
            "options": [
                "all viewers can interpret what is on the screen"
            ],
            "answer": "all viewers can interpret what is on the screen"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A204",
            "question": "Viewing tasks are broken down by what?",
            "options": [
                "8 when the viewers will generally observe content. 6 when the viewers will inspect content with clues and generally observe content. 4 when the viewers will inspect content without clues."
            ],
            "answer": "8 when the viewers will generally observe content. 6 when the viewers will inspect content with clues and generally observe content. 4 when the viewers will inspect content without clues."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A205",
            "question": "What is the formula for throw distance?",
            "options": [
                "Screen Width X Throw Ratio = Distance"
            ],
            "answer": "Screen Width X Throw Ratio = Distance"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A206",
            "question": "What is a work breakdown structure?",
            "options": [
                "a deliverable-oriented grouping of project elements which will ultimately organize and define the total scope of the project."
            ],
            "answer": "a deliverable-oriented grouping of project elements which will ultimately organize and define the total scope of the project."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A207",
            "question": "What is a logic network diagram?",
            "options": [
                "used when negotiating with your client regarding what other tasks need to be done before you can begin your tasks"
            ],
            "answer": "used when negotiating with your client regarding what other tasks need to be done before you can begin your tasks"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A208",
            "question": "When creating estimates for an AV project, what are the primary considerations?",
            "options": [
                "Equipment and material costs, labor costs, estimate markup"
            ],
            "answer": "Equipment and material costs, labor costs, estimate markup"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A209",
            "question": "What is the main objective of evaluating the cost of completing an AV project?",
            "options": [
                "To determine if the AV company made money on the project"
            ],
            "answer": "To determine if the AV company made money on the project"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A210",
            "question": "Which of the following documents would an AV company submit in the event that a modification in the building design impacted the AV system installation requirements?",
            "options": [
                "RFC"
            ],
            "answer": "RFC"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A211",
            "question": "How far can RS-422 run and to how many devices",
            "options": [
                "4000 ft and up to 10 devices"
            ],
            "answer": "4000 ft and up to 10 devices"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A212",
            "question": "How many connectors do you need to connect an RS-232",
            "options": [
                "3 wires 2-3-5"
            ],
            "answer": "3 wires 2-3-5"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A213",
            "question": "When applying the inverse square law to measurements of sound pressure level,",
            "options": [
                "A doubling of distance correlates to a loss of 6dB."
            ],
            "answer": "A doubling of distance correlates to a loss of 6dB."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A214",
            "question": "With light, amplitude is perceived as",
            "options": [
                "Brightness"
            ],
            "answer": "Brightness"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A215",
            "question": "What is the standards for measuring light?",
            "options": [
                "Candela, Lux, Nits"
            ],
            "answer": "Candela, Lux, Nits"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A216",
            "question": "Screen gain is:",
            "options": [
                "Is the ability of a screen to redirect projected light to the audience to make it appear brighter."
            ],
            "answer": "Is the ability of a screen to redirect projected light to the audience to make it appear brighter."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A217",
            "question": "Another way to signify an aspect ratio of 4:3 would be",
            "options": [
                "1.33:1"
            ],
            "answer": "1.33:1"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A218",
            "question": "Composite video is made",
            "options": [
                "by combining the luminance and chroma information onto one cable"
            ],
            "answer": "by combining the luminance and chroma information onto one cable"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A219",
            "question": "Resistance is",
            "options": [
                "The opposition to the flow of electrons in Direct Current."
            ],
            "answer": "The opposition to the flow of electrons in Direct Current."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A220",
            "question": "XLR connectors are",
            "options": [
                "Most commonly used with three conductors plus an outer shell that shields the connection and locks with mating connectors."
            ],
            "answer": "Most commonly used with three conductors plus an outer shell that shields the connection and locks with mating connectors."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A221",
            "question": "The study of sound-wave motion and sound behavior is the science of",
            "options": [
                "Acoustics."
            ],
            "answer": "Acoustics."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A222",
            "question": "Modulating a composite video signal for transportation is commonly referred to as",
            "options": [
                "RF transmission."
            ],
            "answer": "RF transmission."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A223",
            "question": "The changing of direction of a light or sound ray is called",
            "options": [
                "Refraction."
            ],
            "answer": "Refraction."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A224",
            "question": "Which type of front screen has a smooth non-gloss surface similar to a white sheet, provides good color rendition, and evenly disperses light?",
            "options": [
                "Matte"
            ],
            "answer": "Matte"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A225",
            "question": "In a cable, the dielectric",
            "options": [
                "Directly proportional to the voltage and inversely proportional resistance."
            ],
            "answer": "Directly proportional to the voltage and inversely proportional resistance."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A226",
            "question": "What are the 4 teams that comprise the AV Project Team",
            "options": [
                "Owner, Designer, Installer and Facility Management"
            ],
            "answer": "Owner, Designer, Installer and Facility Management"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A227",
            "question": "Who makes up the management team in an AV project",
            "options": [
                "Developer, Construction Manager, and Building Management Agency"
            ],
            "answer": "Developer, Construction Manager, and Building Management Agency"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A228",
            "question": "The End-User, Facility Manager and Building Committee comprise which team within the Project Team",
            "options": [
                "Owner"
            ],
            "answer": "Owner"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A229",
            "question": "What group represents the generic roles that are important to the Project process?",
            "options": [
                "Project Manager, Designers, and Installers"
            ],
            "answer": "Project Manager, Designers, and Installers"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A230",
            "question": "What project characteristics must be considered in order to determine which method is best suited for a particular project?",
            "options": [
                "Schedule, Size, Type, Complexity, and Procurement Requirements"
            ],
            "answer": "Schedule, Size, Type, Complexity, and Procurement Requirements"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A231",
            "question": "Whether a construction project is large or small, which milestones must be achieved in a typical schedule",
            "options": [
                "Programming, Building Design, AV Bid, and Move-In"
            ],
            "answer": "Programming, Building Design, AV Bid, and Move-In"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A232",
            "question": "If a system meets the original design, fulfills the needs of the end-user, and remains in proper working order, what will be the result?",
            "options": [
                "A successful project"
            ],
            "answer": "A successful project"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A233",
            "question": "When is the best time to train users during the System Commissioning and Training Phase of a project?",
            "options": [
                "After the system is complete"
            ],
            "answer": "After the system is complete"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A234",
            "question": "What are the primary functions of Step Four of the System Commissioning and Training Phase of a project?",
            "options": [
                "Inspecting, Testing and Aligning"
            ],
            "answer": "Inspecting, Testing and Aligning"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A235",
            "question": "During which step in the System Commissioning and Training Phase is the final checklist for the complete installation generated?",
            "options": [
                "Generate the Punch List"
            ],
            "answer": "Generate the Punch List"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A236",
            "question": "Verification and Optimization are two concepts that are applied during System Commissioning to ensure that:",
            "options": [
                "The design intent has been met"
            ],
            "answer": "The design intent has been met"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A237",
            "question": "What is the last step of the Construction Phase",
            "options": [
                "Systems Training"
            ],
            "answer": "Systems Training"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A238",
            "question": "During the Construction Phase of a project, which step always follows AV System Testing?",
            "options": [
                "Site Installation"
            ],
            "answer": "Site Installation"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A239",
            "question": "During the Design Phase, what are three major coordination efforts that need to be addressed between the AV designer and the base building design team?",
            "options": [
                "Space Planning, Data/Telecom, and Administrative Coordination"
            ],
            "answer": "Space Planning, Data/Telecom, and Administrative Coordination"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A240",
            "question": "When including GUI Layouts into the Design Documents, which of the following should also be included for optimum usability?",
            "options": [
                "Button-by-Button Functionality"
            ],
            "answer": "Button-by-Button Functionality"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A241",
            "question": "The Owner Plays what role in the Project Lifecycle",
            "options": [
                "Buyer of the AV System"
            ],
            "answer": "Buyer of the AV System"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A242",
            "question": "The Generic project process contains three roles Installer, Project manager and",
            "options": [
                "Designer"
            ],
            "answer": "Designer"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A243",
            "question": "What stages are in both small and large construction projects",
            "options": [
                "Program, Design, Construction and Occupy"
            ],
            "answer": "Program, Design, Construction and Occupy"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A244",
            "question": "What type of project is suitable for a Consultant led design build",
            "options": [
                "6 months or less"
            ],
            "answer": "6 months or less"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A245",
            "question": "What type of project is suitable for an integrator Led Design build",
            "options": [
                "Three months or less"
            ],
            "answer": "Three months or less"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A246",
            "question": "What is the disadvantages of splitting the AV Equipment Contract and Labor contract",
            "options": [
                "Determining which party is responsible for AV system problems"
            ],
            "answer": "Determining which party is responsible for AV system problems"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A247",
            "question": "In the building process what is the first milestone",
            "options": [
                "Issue request for proposal"
            ],
            "answer": "Issue request for proposal"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A248",
            "question": "The purpose of a written program report is to communicate",
            "options": [
                "a functional system description"
            ],
            "answer": "a functional system description"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A249",
            "question": "After witting the program report what is the next step in the program phase",
            "options": [
                "Distribute the report"
            ],
            "answer": "Distribute the report"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A250",
            "question": "The program reports executive summary should contain a brief overview of the project and",
            "options": [
                "Programming process"
            ],
            "answer": "Programming process"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A251",
            "question": "At the beginning of Program Phase which categories of existing documentation should be reviewed",
            "options": [
                "Architectural, Organizational and Technical"
            ],
            "answer": "Architectural, Organizational and Technical"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A252",
            "question": "The purpose of developing an AV system design package is to communicate the",
            "options": [
                "Intent of the design to the installers"
            ],
            "answer": "Intent of the design to the installers"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A253",
            "question": "Which team members best reflect the team of participants during the review step of an AV projects design phase",
            "options": [
                "Architect, Owner, Construction manager and End user"
            ],
            "answer": "Architect, Owner, Construction manager and End user"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A254",
            "question": "During the design phase it is important to coordinate with who",
            "options": [
                "Architect, Electrical consultant, and construction manager"
            ],
            "answer": "Architect, Electrical consultant, and construction manager"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A255",
            "question": "During the System Commissioning and training phase, what is the role of the punch or checklist",
            "options": [
                "It defines the items that require resolution for project completion"
            ],
            "answer": "It defines the items that require resolution for project completion"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A256",
            "question": "In the system commissioning process why is facility inspection important?",
            "options": [
                "The condition of the site and completed AV work can be inspected"
            ],
            "answer": "The condition of the site and completed AV work can be inspected"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A257",
            "question": "What are the 5 parts to determining the End Users Needs",
            "options": [
                "Talk to Stakeholders, Review Existing Documentation, Evaluate the Site Environment, Conduct Program meetings, Write the program report"
            ],
            "answer": "Talk to Stakeholders, Review Existing Documentation, Evaluate the Site Environment, Conduct Program meetings, Write the program report"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A258",
            "question": "What documentation should you get from Stakeholders",
            "options": [
                "Engineering Drawings, Archtectural Organizational project, Design manuals, best practices."
            ],
            "answer": "Engineering Drawings, Archtectural Organizational project, Design manuals, best practices."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A259",
            "question": "What are the 5 parts of the Program Report",
            "options": [
                "Executive Summary, System Descriptions, Infrastructure Considerations, Audio Visual Budgets, Additional Costs"
            ],
            "answer": "Executive Summary, System Descriptions, Infrastructure Considerations, Audio Visual Budgets, Additional Costs"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A260",
            "question": "The needs analysis determines:",
            "options": [
                "Nature of the System, Infrastructure, System Budget"
            ],
            "answer": "Nature of the System, Infrastructure, System Budget"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A261",
            "question": "How does the AV team use information about any identified constraints to the AV design and installation tasks?",
            "options": [
                "To develop a work-around plan when these constraints will affect the design or installation tasks"
            ],
            "answer": "To develop a work-around plan when these constraints will affect the design or installation tasks"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A262",
            "question": "The task level variable refers to",
            "options": [
                "what the observer is trying to see and understand"
            ],
            "answer": "what the observer is trying to see and understand"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A263",
            "question": "What is this formula for? dB = 10 * log(P1/Pr)",
            "options": [
                "Power"
            ],
            "answer": "Power"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A264",
            "question": "What is this formula for? dB = 20 * log(D1/D2)",
            "options": [
                "Distance of SPL"
            ],
            "answer": "Distance of SPL"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A265",
            "question": "What is this formula for? dB = 20 * log(V1/Vr)",
            "options": [
                "Voltage"
            ],
            "answer": "Voltage"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A266",
            "question": "What are considerations to consider when selecting an AV provider",
            "options": [
                "Current workload, Company Credentials and Employee work experience"
            ],
            "answer": "Current workload, Company Credentials and Employee work experience"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A267",
            "question": "Purpose of an AV system",
            "options": [
                "the communication task it helps accomplish"
            ],
            "answer": "the communication task it helps accomplish"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A268",
            "question": "Control System",
            "options": [
                "a subsystem that enables simplified operation of other complex systems such as an av or lighting system. Includes user interface, processor or computer, control equipment."
            ],
            "answer": "a subsystem that enables simplified operation of other complex systems such as an av or lighting system. Includes user interface, processor or computer, control equipment."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A269",
            "question": "Ergonomics",
            "options": [
                "scientific study of the way people interact with a system."
            ],
            "answer": "scientific study of the way people interact with a system."
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A270",
            "question": "Closest viewer rule",
            "options": [
                "no closer than 1X the screen's width"
            ],
            "answer": "no closer than 1X the screen's width"
        },
        {
            "id": "E1A271",
            "question": "Farthest viewer rule",
            "options": [
                "No farther than 8X the screen's height"
            ],
            "answer": "No farther than 8X the screen's height"
        }
    ]
}
